<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Inspiring Quotes</string>

    <!-- Menu Items -->
    <string name="action_full_list">Full List</string>
    <string name="action_random">Random Quote</string>

    <!-- Settings Activity Layout -->
    <string name="color_title">Color</string>
    <string name="size_title">Text Size</string>
    <string name="font_title">Font</string>
    <string name="other_title">Other</string>
    <string name="default_color">Red</string>
    <string name="default_size">12</string>
    <string name="default_font">Normal</string>

    <!-- Dialog Color Items -->
    <string name="pick_color">Pick a color</string>
    <string name="blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="black">Black</string>
    <string name="white">White</string>
    <string name="red">Red</string>

    <!-- Dialog Size Items -->
    <string name="pick_size">Pick a size</string>
    <string name="size10">10</string>
    <string name="size11">11</string>
    <string name="size12">12</string>
    <string name="size13">13</string>
    <string name="size14">14</string>
    <string name="size15">15</string>
    <string name="size16">16</string>

    <!-- Dialog Font Items -->
    <string name="pick_font">Pick a font</string>
    <string name="font_normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="font_thin">Thin</string>
    <string name="font_light">Light</string>
    <string name="font_condensed">Condensed</string>


    <!-- Quotes -->
    <string name="q1">"Don\'t ruin a good today by thinking about a bad yesterday."</string>
    <string name="q2">"An entire sea of water can\'t sink a ship unless it gets inside the ship. Similarly the negativity of the world can\'t put you down unless you allow it to get inside you."</string>
    <string name="q3">"You can\'t always change the picture, but you can surely change the frame."</string>
    <string name="q4">"If you\'re going through hell, keep going. - Winston Churchill"</string>
    <string name="q5">"The purpose of fear is to raise your awareness, not to stop your progress."</string>
    <string name="q6">"The tragedy of life is not death, but what we let die inside us while we live."</string>
    <string name="q7">"The best day is today."</string>
    <string name="q8">"Discipline is just choosing between what you want now and what you want most."</string>
    <string name="q9">"It\'s going to be hard, but hard is not impossible."</string>
    <string name="q10">"A bird sitting on a tree is never afraid of the branch breaking because her trust is not within the branch, but within her wings. Believe in yourself."</string>
    <string name="q11">"It is impossible to live without failing at something, unless you live so cautiously that you might as well not have lived at all - in which case, you fail by default. - J.K. Rowling"</string>
    <string name="q12">"Work until your idols become your rivals."</string>
    <string name="q13">"Great men are not born great, they grow great."</string>
    <string name="q14">"When life puts you in tough situations, don\'t say \'why me.\' Just say \'try me.\'"</string>
    <string name="q15">"Life isn\'t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself."</string>
    <string name="q16">"I\'m going to make the rest of my life, the best of my life."</string>
    <string name="q17">"You can\'t stop the waves, but you can learn to surf. - Jon Kabat-Zinn"</string>
    <string name="q18">"Life is the art of drawing without an eraser. - John W. Gardner"</string>
    <string name="q19">"There\'s always room at the top. - Daniel Webster"</string>
    <string name="q20">"Never give up on a dream because of the time it will take to accomplish it. The time will pass anyways. - Earl Nightingale"</string>
    <string name="q21">"You never know what is enough, until you know what is more than enough. - William Blake"</string>
    <string name="q22">"You don\'t have to be better than everybody else, you just have to be better than you were a week ago."</string>
    <string name="q23">"Maturity begins when you can be right without having to prove the other person wrong."</string>
    <string name="q24">"You either suffer the pain of discipline or you suffer the pain of regret."</string>
    <string name="q25">"Words are free, it’s how you use them that might cost you."</string>
    <string name="q26">"We judge others by their actions, but we judge ourselves by our intentions."</string>
    <string name="q27">"Some people live more in 20 years than others do in 80. Its not the time that matters, its the person. - The Doctor"</string>
    <string name="q28">"I always wonder why birds choose to stay in the same place when they can fly anywhere on the earth, then I ask myself the same question. - Harun Yahya"</string>
    <string name="q29">"Would you believe in what you believe in, if you were the only one who believed it?"</string>
    <string name="q30">"We stopped checking for monsters under our beds when we realized they were inside us. - Sam Steven"</string>
    <string name="q31">"Sometimes burning bridges is best. It prevents you from going back to places you should have never visited to begin with."</string>
    <string name="q32">"May the bridges you burn light your way."</string>
    <string name="q33">"We can complain because rose bushes have thorns, or rejoice because thorn bushes have roses. - Abraham Lincoln"</string>
    <string name="q34">"I am the wisest man alive, for I know one thing, and that is that I know nothing. - Oracle of Delphi to Socrates"</string>
    <string name="q35">"It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor. - Seneca"</string>
    <string name="q36">"Its very easy to scare people, remarkably difficult to unscare them."</string>
    <string name="q37">"Everyone who\'s ever had a shower has had a good idea. It\'s the people who dry off and do something about it that make a difference. - Nolan Bushnell"</string>
    <string name="q38">"Ideas are a commodity. Execution of them is not. - Michael Dell"</string>
    <string name="q39">"All men dream: but not equally. Those who dream by night in the dusty recesses of their minds wake in the day to find that it was vanity: but the dreamers of the day are dangerous men, for they may act their dreams with open eyes, to make it possible. - T. E. Lawrence."</string>
    <string name="q40">"Luck is a concept invented by weak people to explain their failures. - Ron Swanson"</string>
    <string name="q41">"Often times people who are being brutally honest are more interested in being brutal than being honest."</string>
    <string name="q42">"However, I continue to try and I continue, indefatigably, to reach out. There\'s no way I can singlehandedly save the world or, perhaps, even make a perceptible difference - but how ashamed I would be to let a day pass without making one more effort. - Isaac Asimov"</string>
    <string name="q43">"Comparison is the thief of joy."</string>
    <string name="q44">"Anyone can deal with victory. Only the mighty can bear defeat."</string>
    <string name="q45">"Don\'t promise when you\'re happy. Don\'t reply when you\'re angry. Don\'t decide when you\'re sad."</string>
    <string name="q46">"The acid of bitterness eats the container that holds it."</string>
    <string name="q47">"Life becomes easier when you learn to accept the apology you never got."</string>
    <string name="q48">"The happiness of your life depends on the quality of your thoughts. - Marcus Aurelius"</string>
    <string name="q49">"Breathe, it\'s just a bad day. Not a bad life."</string>
    <string name="q50">"If people are not laughing at your goals, your goals are too small. - Azim Premji"</string>
    <string name="q51">"You are to yourself what your thoughts are, you are to others what your actions are."</string>
    <string name="q52">"No matter how bad the day is, it\'s still better than the day you never see."</string>
    <string name="q53">"If you change nothing, nothing will change."</string>
    <string name="q54">"Forgive others, not because they deserve forgiveness, but because you deserve peace. - Jonathan Lockwood Huie"</string>
    <string name="q55">"The sooner you step away from your comfort zone; the sooner you\'ll realize that it really wasn\'t all that comfortable. - Eddie Harris Jr"</string>
    <string name="q56">"Anger, if not restrained, is frequently more hurtful to us than the injury that provokes it. - Seneca"</string>
    <string name="q57">"Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value. –Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="q58">"“Creativity takes courage.” ~Henri Matisse"</string>
    <string name="q59">"“Creativity is intelligence having fun.” ~Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="q60">"“If I create from the heart, nearly everything works; if from the head, almost nothing.” ~Marc Chagall"</string>
    <string name="q61">"“Do not be satisfied with the stories that come before you. Unfold your own myth.” ~Rumi"</string>
    <string name="q62">"“Learn from yesterday, live for today, look to tomorrow, rest this afternoon.” ~Charles M. Schulz"</string>
    <string name="q63">"“Everything in life comes to you as a teacher. Pay Attention. Learn Quickly.” ~Cherokee saying"</string>
    <string name="q64">"“Mistakes are the portals of discovery” ~James Joyce"</string>
    <string name="q65">"“Failure is a bruise, not a tattoo.” ~Jon Sinclair"</string>
    <string name="q66">"“A man can fail many times, but he isn’t a failure until he begins to blame somebody else.” ~John Burroughs"</string>
    <string name="q67">"“When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be.” ~Lao Tzu"</string>
    <string name="q68">" Tomorrow is often the busiest day of the week.—Spanish Proverb"</string>
    <string name="q69">"I’ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I’ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times I’ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I’ve failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed. –Michael Jordan"</string>
    <string name="q70">"Life is what happens to you while you’re busy making other plans. –John Lennon"</string>
    <string name="q71">"Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn’t do than by the ones you did do, so throw off the bowlines, sail away from safe harbor, catch the trade winds in your sails.  Explore, Dream, Discover. –Mark Twain"</string>
    <string name="q72">"Your time is limited, so don’t waste it living someone else’s life. –Steve Jobs"</string>
    <string name="q73">"Winning isn’t everything, but wanting to win is. –Vince Lombardi"</string>
    <string name="q74">"Every child is an artist.  The problem is how to remain an artist once he grows up. –Pablo Picasso"</string>
    <string name="q75">"You can never cross the ocean until you have the courage to lose sight of the shore. –Christopher Columbus"</string>
    <string name="q76">" I’ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel. –Maya Angelou"</string>
    <string name="q77">"Either you run the day, or the day runs you. –Jim Rohn"</string>
    <string name="q78">" Whatever you can do, or dream you can, begin it.  Boldness has genius, power and magic in it. –Johann Wolfgang von Goethe"</string>
    <string name="q79">"The best revenge is massive success. –Frank Sinatra"</string>
    <string name="q80">" People often say that motivation doesn’t last. Well, neither does bathing.  That’s why we recommend it daily. –Zig Ziglar"</string>
    <string name="q81">"Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one’s courage. –Anais Nin"</string>
    <string name="q82">"The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be. –Ralph Waldo Emerson"</string>
    <string name="q83">"Go confidently in the direction of your dreams.  Live the life you have imagined. –Henry David Thoreau"</string>
    <string name="q84">" Certain things catch your eye, but pursue only those that capture the heart. – Ancient Indian Proverb"</string>
    <string name="q85">"Believe you can and you’re halfway there. –Theodore Roosevelt"</string>
    <string name="q86">"Everything you’ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear. –George Addair"</string>
    <string name="q87">"You can’t fall if you don’t climb.  But there’s no joy in living your whole life on the ground. –Unknown"</string>
    <string name="q88">"I have been impressed with the urgency of doing. Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Being willing is not enough; we must do. –Leonardo da Vinci"</string>
    <string name="q89">"In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure. –Bill Cosby"</string>
    <string name="q90">"A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new. – Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="q91">"There are no traffic jams along the extra mile. –Roger Staubach"</string>
    <string name="q92">"I would rather die of passion than of boredom. –Vincent van Gogh"</string>
    <string name="q93">"If you want your children to turn out well, spend twice as much time with them, and half as much money. –Abigail Van Buren"</string>
    <string name="q94">"Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs. –Farrah Gray"</string>
    <string name="q95">"I have learned over the years that when one’s mind is made up, this diminishes fear. –Rosa Parks"</string>
    <string name="q96">"Dreaming, after all, is a form of planning. –Gloria Steinem"</string>
    <string name="q97">" You may be disappointed if you fail, but you are doomed if you don’t try. –Beverly Sills"</string>
    <string name="q98">"The question isn’t who is going to let me; it’s who is going to stop me. –Ayn Rand"</string>
    <string name="q99">"When everything seems to be going against you, remember that the airplane takes off against the wind, not with it. –Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="q100">" Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing. –Benjamin Franklin"</string>




</resources>
